<idea-plugin>
  <id>com.andrewbrookins.wrap_to_column</id>
  <name>Wrap to Column</name>
  <version>1.9.4</version>
  <vendor email="a@andrewbrookins.com" url="http://andrewbrookins.com">Andrew Brookins</vendor>

  <description><![CDATA[
    <p>
      Wraps text to the specified column width. Similar to the Emacs command
      'Fill Paragraph' and Vim's `gq` (format lines) command. This is a replacement
      for the native Intellij Fill Paragraph command, which doesn't work quite
      how I need it to.
    </p>
    <p>
      This plugin provides two IDE actions:
      <ul>
        <li>
          <strong>Wrap Line to Column</strong>: Wraps selected text or the current line if no
          text is selected.
        </li>
        <li>
          <strong>Wrap Paragraph to Column</strong>: Wraps selected text or the paragraph in
          which the cursor appears. A paragraph is defined as text offset by blank lines --
          including lines that only start with what looks like comment syntax (e.g., `//`).
        </li>
      </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
      <strong>Note:</strong> As of version 1.0, this plugin supports only IDEA
      14.1.x-based products and later (e.g., PyCharm 4.1, WebStorm 10, Android
      Studio 1.3).
    </p>
      ]]></description>

  <change-notes><![CDATA[
    <b>1.9.4</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Fixed wrapping for comments with tab indentation. (Issue #73, thanks @Grimeh!)</li>
    <li>Fixed inline comments adding extraneous newlines. (Issue #74, thanks @Grimeh!)</li>
    <li>Fixed selections ending with multiple newlines adding an extra newline.</li>
    </ul>

    <b>1.9.3</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Fixed a bug where wrapping code with inline comments would remove comment markers from continuation lines. (Issue #72, thanks @edgarsi!)</li>
    <li>Fixed Python docstring wrapping when content is on the same line as the opening quotes. (Issue #65, thanks @edgarsi!)</li>
    <li>Added support for wrapping Rust parent line comments (<code>//!</code>). (Issue #52, thanks @mshroyer!)</li>
    <li>Restored optional column width override setting. (Issue #68, thanks @Grimeh!)</li>
    </ul>

     <b>1.9.2</b>
    <ul>
     <li>
     Fixed a bug that prevented the settings panel from loading.
    </li>
    <li>
    From 1.9.0: Wrap Paragraph to Column and Wrap Line to Column now work the same way
    when you select text: the selected text will be wrapped. They differ only when you do
    not select text. Wrap Paragraph to Column will wrap the current paragraph, and Wrap
    Line to Column will wrap the current line.
    </li>
    <li>
    Fixed a bug that incorrectly wrapped code adjacent to comments. You no
    longer have to select a comment directly adjacent to code to avoid wrapping
    the code as well. Instead, Wrap Paragraph to Column will wrap only the
    comment.
    </li>
    <li>
    Fixed Markdown blockquote wrapping.
    </li>
    <li>
    Fixed <code>com.intellij.diagnostic.PluginException: `ActionUpdateThread.OLD_EDT` is deprecated and going to be removed soon. 'com.andrewbrookins.idea.wrap.WrapAction' must override `getActionUpdateThread()` and chose EDT or BGT. See ActionUpdateThread javadoc. [Plugin: com.andrewbrookins.wrap_to_column]</code>
    </ul>

    <b>1.9.0</b>
    <ul>
    <li>
      Wrap Paragraph to Column and Wrap Line to Column now work the same way when
      you select text: the selected text will be wrapped. They differ only when
      you do not select text. Wrap Paragraph to Column will wrap the current
      paragraph, and Wrap Line to Column will wrap the current line.
    </li>
    <li>
      Refactor plugin internals to use AnAction instead of deprecated `execute`
      method.
    </li>
    </ul>

    <b>1.8.0</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Fix plugin to support new Intellij versions</li>
    </ul>

    <b>1.7.0</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Add better support for wrapping lists in Markdown, AsciiDoc, and .txt files</li>
    <li>Ignore most comment-like symbols in Markdown, AsciiDoc, and .txt files (these symbols are used for formatting, not comments, in these documents)</li>
    <li>Fix a regression in wrapping to the configured IDE right margin</li>
    <li>Fix many cases of Wrap Paragraph to Column action wrapping code before or after a comment</li>
    <li>Fix an issue that required you to select an entire line in order to reflow correctly if there was leading whitespace</li>
    </ul>

    <b>1.6.0</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Support SQL comments. Thanks, Elijah Carrel!</li>
    </ul>

    <b>1.5.0</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Fix plugin XML compatibility with newer Intellij versions.</li>
    <li>Special thanks to <b>Edgars Irmejs</b> and <b>Aleksei Kniazev</b> for fixes!</li>
    </ul>

    <b>1.4.0</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Add a new action: Wrap Paragraph to Column.</li>
    </ul>
    <b>1.3.2</b>

    <ul>
    <li>Add a keyboard shortcut for Windows.</li>
    </ul>

    <b>1.3.1</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Fix "kotlin/jvm/internal/Intrinsics" error found in Intellij 14.1.x-based editors.</li>
    </ul>

    <b>1.3.0</b>
    <ul>
    <li>New feature: Use an optional "minimum raggedness" algorithm. You can enable this in Tools -> Wrap to Column.</li>
    </ul>

    <b>1.2.0</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Reflow text containing tabs based on the configured tab width setting.</li>
    </ul>

    <b>1.1.0</b>
    <ul>
    <li>New feature: Set a column width override in Settings: Tools -> Wrap to Column. Overrides style and global column width settings.</li>
    </ul>

    <b>1.0.1</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Fix a bug in handling continuations of C-style multi-line comments</li>
    </ul>

    <b>1.0</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Use the language-specific right margin setting if one is configured</li>
    </ul>

    <b>0.1.4</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Strip trailing spaces before wrapping</li>
    <li>Preserve paragraphs within comments</li>
    </ul>

    <b>0.1.3</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Stop adding an erroneous leading space if the first line of the selection is a newline/carriage return.<li>
    <li>Detect the period "." as a bullet point indentation.</li>
    </ul>

    <b>0.1.2</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Fix plugin for Windows users</l>
    </ul>

    <b>0.1.1</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Better support for multi-line C-style comments.</li>
    </ul>

    <b>0.1</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Initial commit.</li>
    </ul>
      ]]>
  </change-notes>

  <!-- please see http://confluence.jetbrains.net/display/IDEADEV/Build+Number+Ranges for description -->
  <idea-version since-build="222.3345.118"/>

  <!-- please see http://confluence.jetbrains.net/display/IDEADEV/Plugin+Compatibility+with+IntelliJ+Platform+Products
       on how to target different products -->
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>

  <application-components>
      <component>
        <implementation-class>com.andrewbrookins.idea.wrap.config.WrapSettingsState</implementation-class>
      </component>
  </application-components>

  <project-components>
    <!-- Add your project components here -->
  </project-components>


  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <applicationConfigurable
            groupId="tools"
            displayName="Wrap to Column"
            id="wrap.settings"
            instance="com.andrewbrookins.idea.wrap.config.WrapSettingsConfigurable"/>
  </extensions>


  <actions>
    <!-- Add your actions here -->
    <action id="com.andrewbrookins.idea.wrap.WrapAction" class="com.andrewbrookins.idea.wrap.WrapAction"
            text="Wrap Line to Column"
            description="Wrap selected text or current line to the currently configured column width.">
      <add-to-group group-id="EditMenu" anchor="last"/>
      <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default" first-keystroke="shift ctrl meta W"/>
      <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default" first-keystroke="shift ctrl alt W"/>
    </action>

    <action id="com.andrewbrookins.idea.wrap.WrapParagraphAction" class="com.andrewbrookins.idea.wrap.WrapParagraphAction"
            text="Wrap Paragraph to Column"
            description="Wrap paragraph to the currently configured column width.">
      <add-to-group group-id="EditMenu" anchor="last"/>
      <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default" first-keystroke="shift ctrl meta P"/>
      <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default" first-keystroke="shift ctrl alt P"/>
    </action>
  </actions>
</idea-plugin>
